// Answer text must be under 25 characters otherwise they'll be truncated
// Answer value but be the lowercase LETTER of the correct answer (a, b, c, or d)
// All games must be 10 questions - do not delete any!

module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'Which of these things was Jenn NOT yelled at for in Germany?', 
      a: 'Sitting on the ground', 
      b: 'Too many ice cream samples',
      c: 'Flagging down a waiter',
      d: 'Jaywalking',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'Where in Marfa did Jenn trespass with Marcus & Aaron?', 
      a: 'Private art studio', 
      b: 'Private ranch',
      c: 'Private kitchen',
      d: 'Private pool',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which Clearheader stole wine glasses for Jenn from every Fredericksburg winery we went to for Jenn’s 30th bday?', 
      a: 'Shannon', 
      b: 'Devon',
      c: 'Tomi',
      d: 'Jeff',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'Where has Jeff not wrecked a Land Rover?', 
      a: 'Alpine, Utah', 
      b: 'Bastrop, Texas',
      c: 'Provo, Utah',
      d: 'Austin, Texas',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'On a former employer’s work trip, which for the following did Jeff’s boss NOT do? ', 
      a: 'Proposition Jeff’s MIL', 
      b: 'Pee on a taxi',
      c: 'Buy Drugs',
      d: 'Offer drugs to VRBO pres',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'While Jeff & Jenn were in Italy, what attacked Millie (Jenn’s dog)?', 
      a: 'Cat', 
      b: 'Skunk',
      c: 'Bees',
      d: 'Another dog',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Devon broke her ____ while skiing on a band trip?', 
      a: 'Collarbone', 
      b: 'Leg',
      c: 'Dignity',
      d: 'Ribs',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who was not one of Devon’s friends in Saudi Arabia?', 
      a: 'Hebba', 
      b: 'Nadia',
      c: 'Ruevie',
      d: 'Pontus',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'What country has Devon never been to?', 
      a: 'Sri Lanka', 
      b: 'China',
      c: 'Africa, because it’s not a country',
      d: 'Switzerland',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'What did Devon have confiscated at customs in Jedda?', 
      a: 'Bottle of French wine', 
      b: 'Barbie Dolls',
      c: 'Bouncy balls',
      d: 'ESPRIT color-block shirt',
      answer: 'b'
    }
  ]
};